<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="CustomShurt">اللوائح الجمركية على الواردات البنود الشخصية في إقليم أوكرانيا</string>
    <string name="Phrase">Small Text</string>
    <string name="TextCurs">بالطبع:</string>
    <string name="aboutus">حول بنا</string>
    <string name="action_settings">الإعدادات</string>
    <string name="allinfoShort">معلومات عامة عن أوكرانيا</string>
    <string name="allinfoTit">معلومات عامة</string>
    <string name="beforArrive">قبل وصوله</string>
    <string name="cafe">مقهى</string>
    <string name="calculShirtDescr">حساب كم سيكلف رحلتك</string>
    <string name="calculaTitle">تكلف</string>
    <string name="calculate">حساب</string>
    <string name="calculateting">حساب</string>
    <string name="callairoport">مطار بوريسبيل</string>
    <string name="callbutton">دعوة</string>
    <string name="callmedic">سيارة إسعاف</string>
    <string name="callpizza">توصيل البيتزا</string>
    <string name="callpolice">قوات الشرطة</string>
    <string name="comunicShort">الهاتف المحمول والإنترنت في أوكرانيا</string>
    <string name="comunical">وسائل النقل العام</string>
    <string name="comunisTit">الإنترنت والاتصالات</string>
    <string name="curenccyConvet">تحويل العملات</string>
    <string name="cursLabel">"Rate: "</string>
    <string name="customTit">التخليص الجمركي</string>
    <string name="daystey">أيام الإقامة:</string>
    <string name="diferencurs">قد يكون المعدل الحالي مختلفة</string>
    <string name="diferensumm">قد تختلف كمية اعتمادا على الموسم</string>
    <string name="discount">خصومات</string>
    <string name="email_subdject">مساعد أجل</string>
    <string name="email_text">أريد استخدام خدماتك</string>
    <string name="fastfood">لوجبات السريعة</string>
    <string name="firedept">دائرة النار</string>
    <string name="fud">قوة</string>
    <string name="glavotdel">ساحة الاستقلال</string>
    <string name="hostel">نزل</string>
    <string name="hotel">فندق</string>
    <string name="imigratTit">وائح الهجرة</string>
    <string name="imigrateShort">قواعد عند وصوله إلى أراضي أوكرانيا</string>
    <string name="in">ال</string>
    <string name="informationcall">خلفية</string>
    <string name="kartakiev">خريطة المترو كييف</string>
    <string name="kievmap">خريطة</string>
    <string name="living">الإقامة</string>
    <string name="marshruty">طرق سياحية</string>
    <string name="metrokharkov">المترو خريطة خاركوف</string>
    <string name="metrokiev">خريطة المترو كييف</string>
    <string name="metromap">خريطة مترو الأنفاق</string>
    <string name="nightclub">ملهى</string>
    <string name="no">لا</string>
    <string name="pressButton">انقر على الزر أدناه</string>
    <string name="privatdoc">عيادة خاصة 1</string>
    <string name="privatdoc2">عيادة خاصة 2</string>
    <string name="razgovornik">كتاب تفسير العبارات الشائعة</string>
    <string name="send_mail">إرسال متأخرة ...</string>
    <string name="summaLabel">"Amount:  "</string>
    <string name="summatex">"Amount: "</string>
    <string name="taxi">سيارة أجرة</string>
    <string name="taxikv1">2 سيارة أجرة</string>
    <string name="taxikv2">3 سيارة أجرة</string>
    <string name="taxikv3">سيارة أجرة4 </string>
    <string name="textInuah">أدخل المبلغ:</string>
    <string name="textKonvertVal">حدد العملة لتحويل:</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">قبل وصوله</string>
    <string name="transport">نقل</string>
    <string name="usefukll">أرقام هواتف مفيدة</string>
    <string name="usefull">أرقام هواتف مفيدة</string>
    <string name="visaShort">هل تحتاج إلى تأشيرة قبل السفر</string>
    <string name="visaTitle">قواعد دخول</string>
    <string name="visit">رؤية</string>
    <string name="цуддиуыщщт">قريبا!</string>


    <string name="imigrationText">"Prior to or upon landing in Ukraine all non-Ukrainian citizens shall completean immigration form. Forms are available on-board from our cabin crew or at your arrivalairport.  Fill out both the Arrival and Departure information and present the form to the Ukraine ImmigrationOfficer at border control. \nThe immigration card is a document that confirms legality of a foreignersstay on the territory of Ukraine.\nYou should give one part of the form to the customs officer,and keep the other one, then give it to the customs officer while leaving Ukraine.\nThe lack of the immigration card may be the basis for imposing a fine (extracting a bribe) by acustoms officer on the border or the police on the whole territory of Ukraine.\n\nHow to fill in \nThe field meant for the immigration cards number should be left empty \n1. Last name\n2. First name\n3. Citizenship\n4. Date of birth\n5. Sex\n6. Passport no.\n7. If travelling to Ukraine - should be left empty, if transiting to another country - entering thedestination country's visa no. may be required\n8. Children (the ones that accompany you during the trip) - first names and dates of birth\n9. Purpose of the journey - TURYZM (ТУРИЗМ, TOURISM) or TRANZYT (ТРАНЗИТ, TRANSIT)\n10. City, name (and address) of the hotel (hostel) (you can enter anything, the data will not be verified)\n11. Vehicle registration no. (only when travelling by car)\n12. Signature\n\nCaution! Both sides of the form should be filled in. Pay attention that some field numbers fromthe right side are different from those from the left side.\nExample:"

</string>
    <string name="allInfromText">
    "We are glad to invite you to Ukraine. Our country is one of the biggest in Europe and can presentits beautiful landscapes, rich culture, ancient history, delicious cuisine and hospitality. \nHryvnia is a national currency of Ukraine. It has been the national currency since September 2, 1996. \nUkraine is abundant in all tourist attractions for travelers eager to learn more about the surrounding world,peoples inhabiting it, their history and folkways. \nBoundless steppes, thick forests, groves, towering mountains, warm and caressing seas, wide rivers, cave labyrinths– put together, this cannot but attract tourists. Add to this numerous nature preserves, dendrological parks,rich museum collections, historical and cultural landmarks, unique creations of artisans. \nUkraine has substantial economic potential. The key sector of the economy is industry. It accounts for thegreatest part of the national income. Agriculture is important as well. \nThe time in Kiev is 7 hours later than US Eastern Standard, 2 hours later than Greenwich Mean. Ukrainecovers one time zone. Daylight Saving Time is in effect from the first Sunday of April until the lastSunday of October. \nWe hope that you are interested in coming to Ukraine because we would love to have you here in our country.We invite you to enjoy the hospitality of our communities and the beauty of our landscapes! We invite you toappreciate the economic potential of our country! Welcome to Ukraine!" </string>

    <string name="comunicationText">"During your stay in another country it is very important to know about itscommunications system in order to stay in contact with your family and friends back home, as well as to stayin touch with people in the country, itself. Ukraine's communications system is generally well-developed inthe bigger cities and main tourist areas. It's not a problem nowadays to find Internet in Ukraine in themajor cities, but still could be difficult in the smaller towns and villages. You'll be able to findInternet cafés throughout big cities. you'll be able to use Internet in some public places with Wi-Fiaccess: restaurants, cafes, airports, train stations, hotels. They will usually have a Wi-Fi sign onthe window or somewhere else.\n\nMobile\nThere are several companies serving cellular connection in Ukraine:\n\n

        GSM: Kyivstar GSM, MTC Life :)\nCDMA: CDMA Ukraine, Intertelecom, PEOPLE Net, U'TEL (Ukrtelecom)\nMTS-UKR +38050, +38066, +38095, +38099\nKyivstar +38067, +38096, +38097, +38098\nLife:) +38063, +38093\nBeeline +38068\nPeoplenet (CDMA/3g) +38092\nUTEL (3g) +38091\nIntertelecom (CDMA/3g) +38094\nGolden Telecom +38039\n\n

        If your operator works in one of the mentioned above standards, most probably you will be able touse your cell phone in Ukraine as well. Please, find all details from your local cellular provider.\n\n

        Be aware, that international roaming is quite expensive in Ukraine.\nwe highly recommend you on arrival to buy a SIM card from the mobile operators with 3G internet(Kyivstar,MTC Life ) for that would comfortably to Use our application and make your journey more comfortable"</string>

    <string name="customText">"Customs Clearance \nUkraine operates a Red and Green customs system.  Non-residents arriving into Ukraine may use the Green channel provided they are carrying no more than:\n\nEUR10,000 in cash\n1 litre of spirits\n2 litres of wine\n5 litres of beer\n200 cigarettes OR 250 grams of tobacco OR 50 cigars\nFood products for personal use valued up to EUR50\nDo not transport any meat products into Ukraine – these are not allowed into the country.\nThis summary is informational only and rules are subject to change.  It is a passenger's responsibility to comply with all Customs and Immigration laws.  For current information, please"</string>

    <string name="visaText">"Ukraine has a generous visa-waiver program for travellers coming into the country as tourists for stays of UP TO 90 DAYS. Citizens holding passports from the following countries do not need a visa (the list below may not be complete, please check with your embassy):\n\nArmenia, Azerbaijan, Principality of Andorra, Canada, European Union, Republic of Iceland, Republic of Belarus, Japan,Principality of Liechtenstein, Principality of Monaco, Norway, Republic of San Marino, Russian Federation, Switzerland,United Kingdom, United States of America, Vatican City-State\nCIS citizens and holders of diplomatic, special or business passports of select countries that have entered into special agreements with Ukraine do not require a visa for entry.\nAll other foreign citizens require a visa to enter Ukraine.  Please note:  Visas are NOT issued upon arrival and must be obtained in advance through your nearest Embassy of Ukraine. "</string>
    <string name="textmain">"We are glad to invite you to Ukraine. \nProject <b>Travel Ukraine Kiev</b> created, for that would make your trip to Ukraine as comfortable as possible. The app is updated monthly, and every day it becomes more and more interesting. This proposal is developed voluntarily on this app, please tell your friends and like our page.\nWe hope that you are interested in coming to Ukraine because we would love to have you here in our country."</string>
    <string name="clickfirst">تحديد عنصر</string>
    <string name="tittopten">أفضل 10 أشياء يمكن أن يرى في كييف</string>
<string name="top10see">"
   <b> 1. Climb the bell tower of St. Sophia \n \n </b>


        Known for its architecture, St. Sophia Cathedral is the most visited monument of architecture and culture of
        the city. The decoration of the ensemble of the reserve "Sophia of Kyiv" is the bell tower, built in the early
        XVII century. It is decorated with white stucco decorations on a bright turquoise background. The architectural
        image of the bell tower was formed during the XVIII - XIX centuries. The bell tower has 20 bells. On the second
        floor bell kept "Mazeppa", weighing 13 tons, which was cast at the beginning of the XVIII century. to order and
        means of Hetman Ivan Mazepa. \n

        Where: Street. Vladimir, 24, \n \n


        <b>2. Roller skating at the Mariinsky park</b> \n
        Mariinsky Park is known not only refined the Mariinsky Palace, but also serves as a meeting place for skaters
        and skateboarders capital of all ages. Walk along the stadium "Dynamo" with good asphalt is almost entirely in
        the shade. The second part is a roller skating in the park is located opposite the summer theater, known as the
        "Shell". Learn roller skating at the Mariinsky park is a pleasure. But even if you do not ride, you can also walk
        in the shade and relax by the fountain in Mariinsky park. \n

        Where: Mariinsky park \n \n


        <b> 3. Make a wish at the fountain in the courtyard of the Cathedral of St. Michael</b> \n
        St. Michael"s Cathedral was built in the early XII century. in honor of St. Michael the Archangel. In the courtyard
        of the cathedral it is at first glance inconspicuous small fountain - "Fountain Wish." It is next to it you can make
        a wish. To do this, wet and pressed a coin to metal protrusions. If the coin is stuck and not fall, your wish will
        be granted. Some may argue that the secret lies in the strength of the surface tension, but it"s up to you to believe
        in the mysterious power of the fountain or not. \n

        Where: Street. Three Saints, 8 \n\n

        <b>4. Visit Landscape Alley</b>\n

        This park was first opened in May 2011. It soon became a place that attracts residents and visitors to the capital
        of Kiev in Ukraine. Here are the creative imagination and artistic compositions most famous and successful
        Ukrainian designers. Uniqueness, creativity, modernity and beauty - these are some words that can convey only
        a partial impression of the park. \n

        Where: Street. Vladimir, 2 - Str. Zhytomyrska, 34 \n \n


        <b> 5. Walk through Andreevskom</b> \n

        This is one of the oldest streets in Kiev, which connects the lower part of the city with the central
        part of Podil Detinets city. It is likely that the name of the descent was in the XVIII century. from
        St. Andrew"s Church, which was built in this place in 1744 - 1754 years. It is also called Kyiv"s
        Montmartre. Today descent - is the place of the exhibition and sale of paintings and folk art items.
        At Andrew"s descent can buy souvenirs for the whole family, paintings, antiques and various trinkets. \n

        Where: Metro station "Kontraktova Square" from Kontraktova Square - top;
        or descend from St. Michael"s Cathedral on the street Tithe \n \n


        <b> 6. Visit the deepest metro station in the world - "Arsenal", as well as one of the most beautiful metro
            station in Europe - "Golden Gate"</b> \n

        In the capital of Ukraine is the deepest station in the world - "Arsenal", whose depth is 105 meters.
        There is an opinion that it is an absolute world record for metro stations commissioned. "Arsenalnaya"
        put into operation one of the first - in 1960. It received its name from the nearby factory "Arsenal".
        So deep-station had to be built because of the difficult terrain near the Dnieper River. \n


        In addition, while in Kiev, worth a visit ""olden Gate" - the twenty-ninth station of the Kiev Metro.
        Tourist publications «Bootsnall Trevel» she was named one of the 15 most beautiful stations in the world,
        and in 2013 she joined the list of 22 most beautiful stations in Europe by the newspaper "The Daily Telegraph".
        The station was opened in 1989. In the decoration used mosaic, which tells the story of Kievan Rus.
        The decoration is dominated by marble and granite. \n

        Where: Metro station "Arsenal", "Golden Gate" \n \n


       <b> 7. Admire the views during trips teplokhodnye </b>\n
        Boat trip on the Dnieper River will allow escape from the daily routine. Admiring the views of the Dnieper
        you will plunge into distant and memorable times of our history and will be able to admire the view of modern
        Kiev. The greatness of the buildings of Kiev-Pechersk Lavra, the monument to Volodymyr the Great, Vydubitsky
        St. Michael"s Monastery, St. Andrew"s Church and the picturesque landscapes of the Dnipro will remain forever
        in your sweet memories. \n
        Where: Metro Station "Postal Square", pier №8 \n
        How much: from 11:00 to 19:00 - 60 USD. After 19:00 - 80 UAH \n \n
        <b> 8. Visit one of the largest museums in Ukraine</b> \n

        National Museum of the Great Patriotic War of 1941-1945. - One of the largest museums in Ukraine (over 300
        thousand. Pieces), which covers an area of 10 hectares. The memorial complex was opened in 1981 in memory
        of the German-Soviet War of 1941-1945. The museum contains a large bowl "Fire of Glory", an exhibition of
        military equipment and weapons, the main square with the Alley of Hero Cities, and the monument "Motherland"
        (62 meters). \n
        Where: Street. Lavra, 24 \n
        How much: free entrance to the memorial complex \n \n
        <b> 9. Walk caves Kiev-Pechersk Lavra with a candle </b> \n
        Kiev-Pechersk Lavra is one of the main spiritual centers of Orthodox Christianity. The monastery was founded
        in 1051 as a center for spreading the faith, education and spiritual education. On its territory there are
        more than 100 stone structures, 40 of which - the unique architectural monuments: churches, museums, libraries,
        and so on. Kiev-Pechersk Lavra is also the burial place of many prominent historical and religious figures. \n
        Where: Near Caves, the Far Caves \n
        How much: Admission to the (Lower Lavra): free \n
        Access to the (Upper Lavra): 15 UAH. \n \n
        <b> 10. Look at the Golden Gate </b> \n
        The unique monument of defensive architecture of Kievan Rus XI century., Which was part of the powerful
        fortifications and level main entrance to Kiev. In 1750, the gate is in an extremely poor condition. In order
        to preserve the monument from destruction of its mothballed underground. Repair and restoration work carried
        out in 2007 discovered the contemporaries of this unique monument. Today, anyone can look inside the Golden
        Gate and learn actually why they are called "gold» \n
        Where: Street. Vladimir, 40a \n
        How much: 15 UAH \n


        "</string>
    <string name="bestrest">مطاعم المأكولات الأوكرانية في كييف </string>
    <string name="belveder">Restaurant Belveder</string>
    <string name="belveder_ad">Address: Dnieprovsky Spusk1, Kiev</string>
    <string name="carselo_ad">Address:42/1 Ivan Mazepa Street, Kiev(near the Kiev Pechersk Lavra)</string>
    <string name="kureni">Restaurant Kureni</string>
    <string name="kureni_disk">Address:4 Parkova Doroha (Park Alley), Kiev</string>
    <string name="pervak">Pervak Restaurant</string>
    <string name="pervak_ad">Address: 2 Rognedinskaya Street, Kiev</string>
    <string name="puzata">Puzata Hata fast food restaurant</string>
    <string name="puzata_ad">Address:Various locations</string>
    <string name="tsarskoe_selo">Restaurant Tsarskoye Selo</string>
    <string name="one">One</string>
    <string name="pervak_diskr">The Pervak restaurant has succeeded in creating the perfect restaurant for tourists and locals alike, yet has not sacrificed its Ukrainian identity. The exterior of the building is splendid, but behind the door beckons a restaurant full of surprises, smiling faces and tasty dishes. It consists of seven distinct dining areas decorated in its own unique style. This is common in Ukrainian restaurants, they are exceptionally good value and a great way to enjoy a quick meal and check out the place.</string>
    <string name="kureni_diskr">Off the beaten track and hidden away and another restaurant worth seeking out.This is a great place to eat during the warmer months. The restaurant Kurenisits on a hill overlooking the islands on the river Dnipro.It is one of the oldest restaurants in Kiev but numerous facelifts and refurbishments have kept Kureni looking fresh and inviting. It is a perfect place to bring a family, there is a small open-air playground for the children and there is plenty of space to run around in. But it is also large enough to tuck yourself away for a meeting or a quite romantic meal.</string>
    <string name="tasrselo_diskr">The Tsarskoye Selo restaurant is situated near to the Pechersk Lavra and close to the huge Motherland Statue in the heart of historic Kiev. Waiters and waitresses dressed in national costume and an interior that looks like something out of a folk museum. It is unashamedly touristy but somehow manages a kind of classy elegance. Everything is spotlessly clean, the attention to detail, quality of food and standards of service are refreshingly reassuring. It is fair to say that it is a little more expensive than some other restaurants in Kiev, but in comparison to what you would pay back home it will still be a lot cheaper.</string>
    <string name="velveder_disk">Worth visiting just for the view.You can see the Dnipro River, Kiev Pechersk Lavra, Podil and the whole of the left bank from the terrace. Generally the food is pretty good but a little pricy for Kiev.English speaking waitresses and very attentive service.Worth treating yourself as it really does offer stunning views over the city.</string>
    <string name="puzata_disk">This is a great chain of restaurants if you want to snatch a very cheap tasty snack during the daytime. This is the Ukrainian equivalent to Mc donalds, except thatPuzata Hata is ten times better and much more healthy. Food is served to you by staff behind a counter or from tables and fridges placed along the route to the dining area. Its a bit like an up-market version of school dinners but much more fun. This is popular with students and your average local Ukrainian grabbing a bite to eat before returning back to work. You will not find much English spoken here but pointing,smiling and terrible attempts at speaking Ukrainian/Russian are perfectly acceptable.</string>
</resources>