<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Travel Ukraine Kiev</string>

    <string name="hello_world" translatable="false">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps" translatable="false">Map</string>
    <string name="glavotdel">Maidan Nezalezhnosti</string>
    <string name="aboutus">About Us</string>

    <string name="metromap">Subway map</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id" translatable="false">874921642593690</string>
    <string name="callbutton">Call</string>
    <string name="about" translatable="false">Украи́на — государство в Восточной Европе. Население, по итогам переписи 2001 года, составило 48 240 902 постоянных жителей[18] и 48 457 102 человек наличного населения[19], по данным государственной службы статистики Украины на 1 июня 2015 года — 42 667 285 постоянных жителей и 42 836 922 человек наличного населения[11][12], территория в рамках конституционного устройства[10] страны — 603 549 км²[20], при этом часть её властями Украины де-факто не контролируется. Занимает 32-е место в мире по численности населения, 44 (47)-е по территории и второе после России по территории среди стран Европы.\n Столица — Киев. Государственный язык — украинский.\n Украина — унитарное государство и парламентско-президентская республика. 8 июня 2014 года пост президента занял Пётр Порошенко. Премьер-министр Украины — Арсений Яценюк (с 27 февраля 2014 года). Страна подразделяется на 27 административно-территориальных единиц, 24 из которых являются областями, 1 — автономной республикой и 2 представляют собой города государственного подчинения (Киев, Севастополь[22]).\n Граничит с Белоруссией на севере, Польшей, Словакией и Венгрией — на западе, Румынией и Молдавией — на юго-западе, Россией на востоке и северо-востоке. На юге и юго-востоке омывается Чёрным и Азовским морями.\n Большая часть верующих исповедует православие.\n Индустриально-аграрная страна[источник не указан 156 дней]. Объём ВВП за 2012 год, рассчитанный по паритету покупательной способности составил 338 334 миллиона долларов США (7 421 доллара США на душу населения)[13]. Номинальный ВВП в том же году составил 176 310 миллионов долларов США (3 867 долларов США на душу населения)[13]. Денежная единица — гривна (UAH), усреднённый курс за июнь 2015 год — 22 гривны за 1 доллар США.\n Независимость страны от СССР, союзной республикой которого Украина была с декабря 1922 года, провозглашена 24 августа 1991 года. Государство-продолжатель УССР, соправопреемница СССР по международным договорам, соучредитель СССР, ООН, СНГ, ГУАМ, ОЧЭС и других организаций.После 1991 года и до 1994—1996 годов Украина располагала третьим по величине стратегическим ядерным запасом после США и России.</string>
    <string name="usefukll">Useful phone numbers</string>

    <string name="textmain"><![CDATA[We are glad to invite you to Ukraine. \n
<p>Project <b>Travel Ukraine Kiev</b> created, for that would make your trip to Ukraine as comfortable as possible. The app is updated monthly, and every day it becomes more and more interesting. This proposal is developed voluntarily on this app, please tell your friends and layknut our page.</p>\n
    We hope that you are interested in coming to Ukraine because we would love to have you here in our country.
    ]]></string>
    <string name="razgovornik">Phrasebook</string>
    <string name="marshruty">Tourist routes</string>
    <string name="kievmap">Map</string>
    <string name="usefull">Useful phone numbers</string>
    <string name="taxikv1">Taxi Kiev</string>
    <string name="taxikv2">Taxi Kiev 2</string>
    <string name="taxikv3">Taxi Kiev 3</string>
    <string name="privatdoc">Private Ambulance 1</string>
    <string name="privatdoc2">Private Ambulance 2</string>
    <string name="callmedic">Ambulance</string>
    <string name="callpizza">Pizza delivery</string>
    <string name="callpolice">Police</string>
    <string name="firedept">Fire Department</string>
    <string name="informationcall">Information Service</string>
    <string name="callairoport">Borispol airport</string>
    <string name="Phrase">Small Text</string>
    <string name="discount">Discounts</string>
    <string name="цуддиуыщщт">Coming soon!</string>
    <string name="summatex">"Amount: "</string>
    <string name="one" translatable="false">One</string>
    <string name="in">In</string>
    <string name="equal" translatable="false">Is Equal To</string>
    <string name="result" translatable="false">Click Calculate for Result</string>
    <string name="calculate">Calculate</string>
    <string name="curenccyConvet">Currency converter</string>


    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="metrokiev">Subway map of Kiev</string>
    <string name="metrokharkov">Subway map of Kharkov</string>
    <string name="textInuah">Enter the amount in UAH:</string>
    <string name="textKonvertVal">Select a currency for conversion:</string>
    <string name="TextCurs">Rate:</string>
    <string name="pressButton">Click on the button below</string>
    <string name="cursLabel">"Rate: "</string>
    <string name="summaLabel">"Amount:  "</string>
    <string name="beforArrive">Before arriving</string>

    <string name="about2" translatable="false">Украи́на — государство в Восточной Европе. Население, по итогам переписи 2001 года, составило 48 240 902 постоянных жителей[18] и 48 457 102 человек наличного населения[19], по данным государственной службы статистики Украины на 1 июня 2015 года — 42 667 285 постоянных жителей и 42 836 922 человек наличного населения[11][12], территория в рамках конституционного устройства[10] страны — 603 549 км²[20], при этом часть её властями Украины де-факто не контролируется. Занимает 32-е место в мире по численности населения, 44 (47)-е по территории и второе после России по территории среди стран Европы.\n Столица — Киев. Государственный язык — украинский.\n Украина — унитарное государство и парламентско-президентская республика. 8 июня 2014 года пост президента занял Пётр Порошенко. Премьер-министр Украины — Арсений Яценюк (с 27 февраля 2014 года). Страна подразделяется на 27 административно-территориальных единиц, 24 из которых являются областями, 1 — автономной республикой и 2 представляют собой города государственного подчинения (Киев, Севастополь[22]).\n Граничит с Белоруссией на севере, Польшей, Словакией и Венгрией — на западе, Румынией и Молдавией — на юго-западе, Россией на востоке и северо-востоке. На юге и юго-востоке омывается Чёрным и Азовским морями.\n Большая часть верующих исповедует православие.\n Индустриально-аграрная страна[источник не указан 156 дней]. Объём ВВП за 2012 год, рассчитанный по паритету покупательной способности составил 338 334 миллиона долларов США (7 421 доллара США на душу населения)[13]. Номинальный ВВП в том же году составил 176 310 миллионов долларов США (3 867 долларов США на душу населения)[13]. Денежная единица — гривна (UAH), усреднённый курс за июнь 2015 год — 22 гривны за 1 доллар США.\n Независимость страны от СССР, союзной республикой которого Украина была с декабря 1922 года, провозглашена 24 августа 1991 года. Государство-продолжатель УССР, соправопреемница СССР по международным договорам, соучредитель СССР, ООН, СНГ, ГУАМ, ОЧЭС и других организаций.После 1991 года и до 1994—1996 годов Украина располагала третьим по величине стратегическим ядерным запасом после США и России.Украи́на — государство в Восточной Европе. Население, по итогам переписи 2001 года, составило 48 240 902 постоянных жителей[18] и 48 457 102 человек наличного населения[19], по данным государственной службы статистики Украины на 1 июня 2015 года — 42 667 285 постоянных жителей и 42 836 922 человек наличного населения[11][12], территория в рамках конституционного устройства[10] страны — 603 549 км²[20], при этом часть её властями Украины де-факто не контролируется. Занимает 32-е место в мире по численности населения, 44 (47)-е по территории и второе после России по территории среди стран Европы.\n Столица — Киев. Государственный язык — украинский.\n Украина — унитарное государство и парламентско-президентская республика. 8 июня 2014 года пост президента занял Пётр Порошенко. Премьер-министр Украины — Арсений Яценюк (с 27 февраля 2014 года). Страна подразделяется на 27 административно-территориальных единиц, 24 из которых являются областями, 1 — автономной республикой и 2 представляют собой города государственного подчинения (Киев, Севастополь[22]).\n Граничит с Белоруссией на севере, Польшей, Словакией и Венгрией — на западе, Румынией и Молдавией — на юго-западе, Россией на востоке и северо-востоке. На юге и юго-востоке омывается Чёрным и Азовским морями.\n Большая часть верующих исповедует православие.\n Индустриально-аграрная страна[источник не указан 156 дней]. Объём ВВП за 2012 год, рассчитанный по паритету покупательной способности составил 338 334 миллиона долларов США (7 421 доллара США на душу населения)[13]. Номинальный ВВП в том же году составил 176 310 миллионов долларов США (3 867 долларов США на душу населения)[13]. Денежная единица — гривна (UAH), усреднённый курс за июнь 2015 год — 22 гривны за 1 доллар США.\n Независимость страны от СССР, союзной республикой которого Украина была с декабря 1922 года, провозглашена 24 августа 1991 года. Государство-продолжатель УССР, соправопреемница СССР по международным договорам, соучредитель СССР, ООН, СНГ, ГУАМ, ОЧЭС и других организаций.После 1991 года и до 1994—1996 годов Украина располагала третьим по величине стратегическим ядерным запасом после США и России.Украи́на — государство в Восточной Европе. Население, по итогам переписи 2001 года, составило 48 240 902 постоянных жителей[18] и 48 457 102 человек наличного населения[19], по данным государственной службы статистики Украины на 1 июня 2015 года — 42 667 285 постоянных жителей и 42 836 922 человек наличного населения[11][12], территория в рамках конституционного устройства[10] страны — 603 549 км²[20], при этом часть её властями Украины де-факто не контролируется. Занимает 32-е место в мире по численности населения, 44 (47)-е по территории и второе после России по территории среди стран Европы.\n Столица — Киев. Государственный язык — украинский.\n Украина — унитарное государство и парламентско-президентская республика. 8 июня 2014 года пост президента занял Пётр Порошенко. Премьер-министр Украины — Арсений Яценюк (с 27 февраля 2014 года). Страна подразделяется на 27 административно-территориальных единиц, 24 из которых являются областями, 1 — автономной республикой и 2 представляют собой города государственного подчинения (Киев, Севастополь[22]).\n Граничит с Белоруссией на севере, Польшей, Словакией и Венгрией — на западе, Румынией и Молдавией — на юго-западе, Россией на востоке и северо-востоке. На юге и юго-востоке омывается Чёрным и Азовским морями.\n Большая часть верующих исповедует православие.\n Индустриально-аграрная страна[источник не указан 156 дней]. Объём ВВП за 2012 год, рассчитанный по паритету покупательной способности составил 338 334 миллиона долларов США (7 421 доллара США на душу населения)[13]. Номинальный ВВП в том же году составил 176 310 миллионов долларов США (3 867 долларов США на душу населения)[13]. Денежная единица — гривна (UAH), усреднённый курс за июнь 2015 год — 22 гривны за 1 доллар США.\n Независимость страны от СССР, союзной республикой которого Украина была с декабря 1922 года, провозглашена 24 августа 1991 года. Государство-продолжатель УССР, соправопреемница СССР по международным договорам, соучредитель СССР, ООН, СНГ, ГУАМ, ОЧЭС и других организаций.После 1991 года и до 1994—1996 годов Украина располагала третьим по величине стратегическим ядерным запасом после США и России.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">Before arriving</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

            "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion.""The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet ""technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n""Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The ""use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the ""flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical ""world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n""The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, ""interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows ""seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

            "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"


            "3D world.\n\n"

            "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z ""dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the ""positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single ""position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n""On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is ""emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

            "Light and shadow.\n\n"

            "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create ""directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n""Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android ""development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at ""various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the ""y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

            "Resting elevation.\n\n"

            "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation ""that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting ""elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

            "Component elevations.\n\n"


            "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

            "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between ""their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass ""through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, ""whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n""On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. ""For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a ""user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n""On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. ""For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere ""when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    
    <string name="imigrationText">"Prior to or upon landing in Ukraine all non-Ukrainian citizens shall complete 
    an immigration form. Forms are available on-board from our cabin crew or at your arrival 
    airport.  Fill out both the Arrival and Departure information and present the form to the Ukraine Immigration 
    Officer at border control. \n
    The immigration card is a document that confirms legality of a foreigner's 
    stay on the territory of Ukraine.\n
         You should give one part of the form to the customs officer, 
        and keep the other one, then give it to the customs officer while leaving Ukraine.\n
        The lack of the immigration card may be the basis for imposing a fine (extracting a bribe) by a 
        customs officer on the border or the police on the whole territory of Ukraine.\n\n

        <b>How to fill in</b>\n
        The field meant for the immigration card's number should be left empty\n
        1. Last name\n
        2. First name\n
        3. Citizenship\n
        4. Date of birth\n
        5. Sex\n
        6. Passport no.\n
        7. If travelling to Ukraine - should be left empty, if transiting to another country - entering the 
        destination country's visa no. may be required\n
        8. Children (the ones that accompany you during the trip) - first names and dates of birth\n
        9. Purpose of the journey - TURYZM (ТУРИЗМ, TOURISM) or TRANZYT (ТРАНЗИТ, TRANSIT)\n
        10. City, name (and address) of the hotel / hostel (you can enter anything, the data will not be verified)\n
        11. Vehicle registration no. (only when travelling by car)\n
        12. Signature\n\n
        Caution! Both sides of the form should be filled in. Pay attention that some field numbers from 
        the right side are different from those from the left side.\n
        Example:"
</string>
    <string name="allInfromText">
    "We are glad to invite you to Ukraine. Our country is one of the biggest in Europe and can present 
    its beautiful landscapes, rich culture, ancient history, delicious cuisine and hospitality. \n
Hryvnia is a national currency of Ukraine. It has been the national currency since September 2, 1996. \n
Ukraine is abundant in all tourist attractions for travelers eager to learn more about the surrounding world, 
peoples inhabiting it, their history and folkways. \n
Boundless steppes, thick forests, groves, towering mountains, warm and caressing seas, wide rivers, cave labyrinths 
– put together, this cannot but attract tourists. Add to this numerous nature preserves, dendrological parks, 
rich museum collections, historical and cultural landmarks, unique creations of artisans. \n
Ukraine has substantial economic potential. The key sector of the economy is industry. It accounts for the 
greatest part of the national income. Agriculture is important as well. \n
The time in Kiev is 7 hours later than US Eastern Standard, 2 hours later than Greenwich Mean. Ukraine 
covers one time zone. Daylight Saving Time is in effect from the first Sunday of April until the last 
Sunday of October. \n
We hope that you are interested in coming to Ukraine because we would love to have you here in our country. 
We invite you to enjoy the hospitality of our communities and the beauty of our landscapes! We invite you to 
appreciate the economic potential of our country! Welcome to Ukraine!
   " </string>
   
    <string name="comunicationText">"During your stay in another country it is very important to know about its 
    communications system in order to stay in contact with your family and friends back home, as well as to stay 
    in touch with people in the country, itself. Ukraine's communications system is generally well-developed in 
    the bigger cities and main tourist areas. It's not a problem nowadays to find Internet in Ukraine in the 
    major cities, but still could be difficult in the smaller towns and villages. You'll be able to find 
    Internet cafés throughout big cities. you'll be able to use Internet in some public places with Wi-Fi 
    access: restaurants, cafes, airports, train stations, hotels. They will usually have a Wi-Fi sign on 
    the window or somewhere else.\n\n
        Mobile\n
        There are several companies serving cellular connection in Ukraine:\n\n

        GSM: Kyivstar GSM, MTC Life :)\n
        CDMA: CDMA Ukraine, Intertelecom, PEOPLE Net, U'TEL (Ukrtelecom)\n\n

        If your operator works in one of the mentioned above standards, most probably you will be able to 
        use your cell phone in Ukraine as well. Please, find all details from your local cellular provider.\n\n

        Be aware, that international roaming is quite expensive in Ukraine.\n
        we highly recommend you on arrival to buy a SIM card from the mobile operators with 3G internet(Kyivstar, 
        MTC Life ) for that would comfortably to Use our application and make your journey more comfortable
        "</string>

    <string name="customText">"Customs Clearance \n
        Ukraine operates a Red and Green customs system.  Non-residents arriving into Ukraine may use the Green channel provided they are carrying no more than:\n\n
        EUR10,000 in cash\n
        1 litre of spirits\n
        2 litres of wine\n
        5 litres of beer\n
        200 cigarettes OR 250 grams of tobacco OR 50 cigars\n
        Food products for personal use valued up to EUR50\n
        Do not transport any meat products into Ukraine – these are not allowed into the country.\n
        This summary is informational only and rules are subject to change.  It is a passenger's responsibility to comply with all Customs and Immigration laws.  For current information, please
        "</string>

    <string name="visaText">"Ukraine has a generous visa-waiver program for travellers coming into the country as tourists for stays of UP TO 90 DAYS. Citizens holding passports from the following countries do not need a visa (the list below may not be complete, please check with your embassy):\n\n
        Armenia\n
        Azerbaijan\n
        Principality of Andorra\n
        Canada\n
        European Union\n
        Republic of Iceland\n
        Republic of Belarus\n
        Japan\n
        Principality of Liechtenstein\n
        Principality of Monaco\n
        Norway\n
        Republic of San Marino\n
        Russian Federation\n
        Switzerland\n
        United Kingdom\n
        United States of America\n
        Vatican City-State\n
        CIS citizens and holders of diplomatic, special or business passports of select countries that have entered into special agreements with Ukraine do not require a visa for entry.\n
        All other foreign citizens require a visa to enter Ukraine.  Please note:  Visas are NOT issued upon arrival and must be obtained in advance through your nearest Embassy of Ukraine. "</string>
    <string name="calculaTitle">Calculating the cost</string>
    <string name="kartakiev">Subway map of Kiev</string>
    <string name="calculShirtDescr">Calculate how much your trip will cost</string>
    <string name="visaTitle">Visa Requirements</string>
    <string name="visaShort">Do I need to get visa before traveling</string>
    <string name="customTit">Customs Clearance</string>
    <string name="CustomShurt">The right to import and export to the territory of Ukraine</string>
    <string name="imigrateShort">Rules of registration on arrival in the territory of Ukraine</string>
    <string name="comunisTit">Communication</string>
    <string name="comunicShort">Mobile telephony and Internet in Ukraine</string>
    <string name="allinfoTit">General information</string>
    <string name="allinfoShort">General information about Ukraine</string>
    <string name="emailsend">askden8@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="email_subdject">Order Assistance</string>
    <string name="email_text">I wish ro use yours travel assistance</string>
    <string name="send_mail">Sending letter...</string>
    <string name="imigratTit">Immigration Regulations </string>
 <string name="interestFacts">"
10 interesting facts about Ukraine\n
1. The geographical centre of Europe is situated in the territory of Ukraine, not far from the city of Rakhov in Zakarpattia region. \n
2. The grave of the founding rabbi of Hassidism, situated near Uman', is a pilgrimage site for Hasidic Jews. \n
3. The first state constitution in Europe was created by a Ukrainian politician Pylyp Orlyk. On April 5th, 1710 he was elected the Hetman of Zaporozhye troops. On the same day Pylyp Orlyk has announced "the Constitution of the rights and freedoms of Zaporizhye army". For example, U.S. Constitution was adopted in 1787 and French and Polish in 1791. \n
4. The first computer in continental Europe was built in Kiev under the supervision of the scholar Sergey Lebedev and well-known scientist Victor Glushkov in 1950. \n
Ukrainian AN-225 Mria - the biggest and heaviest aircraft in the World. \n
Ukrainian AN-225 Mria as the basis for the aerospace systems. \n
5. AN-225 “Mria” (from Ukrainian – “a dream”) is today the biggest and the heaviest aircraft with the highest cargo capacity in the World. This unique cargo plane was constructed in the 1980′s by the Antonov’s Development Laboratory (Kiev, Ukraine). Its length is 84 m, height – 18 m, total cargo capacity – 250 tons. \n
6. Ukraine contains around 5% of the worlds mineral resources. \n
7. More than 12 million foreign tourists visit Ukraine each year, to see the Carpathian Mountains, the coastline of the Black Sea, the Dnieper River, vineyards, ruins of ancient cities and castles; ancient churches, cathedrals, and monasteries; world-class opera and ballet, and more. \n
8. Ukraine has the World’s 5th largest and fastest growing IT outsourcing services market in the World, with revenues in 2011 expected to reach $1 billion. \n
Modern Ukrainian ethnic song "I know" by Ruslana - Winner of Eurovision Song Contes 2004. \n
9. Famous people that are Ukrainian or of Ukrainian extraction are Vitali and Vladimir Klitschko, Andrey Shevchenko, Vasyl Virastyuk, Sergey Korolev, Vladimir Vernadsky, Ilya Mechnikov, Simon Kuznets, Nikolay Amosov, Mikhail Bulgakov, Ilya Repin, Kazimir Malevich, Sergei Prokofiev, Ruslana and many others. \n
10. The horse was first domesticated on the territory of Ukraine.

 "</string>

</resources>
